

Ian Stephen Gengoni Artis

Software Engineer

Contact Me

Email:

ian.stephen.artis@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ianstephen-artis/

Phone:

+63 923 7388 582

Portfolio:

https://ianartis.github.io/portfolio/index.html

Certificate/s:

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/5 1bdd715-90df-4657-90c0-4ebc1ec7db75/

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/0 c6b2857-d7d6-4d8d-8d01-331faaddf93b/

Skills

- Hard Code Programming
 Javascript, Html, CSS,
 MongoDB, NodeJS, and
 ReactJs
- Low Code Programming -Appian and Outsystem

Character References

- Lewis Karl Penas -Hardware Engineer (Teradyne Phil) -09329014984
- Karl Alemar Cruz -University Instructor (CTU-Barili) -09424360096

Professional Summary



To attain a full-time job wherein I can acquire valuable knowledge and skills to maximize my talents and apply all the skills that I have learned. I would be willing to gain more experiences in any area you feel suitable to my skills and experiences.

Work Experience



Junior Software Engineer

UBX, a company that allows businesses, fintechs, developers and the government to access embeddable solutions and the widest network of financial institutions in the Philippines.

Dec 2021 to Present

• Developing and implementing software solutions based on client requirements

Intern - Engineering Technician

Teradyne Philippines Limited Sep 2018 to May 2019 (9 months)

- Learned about the operations of the company's software programming team
- Coordinated communications between multiple departments

Education



Bootcamp

Full Stack Web Development (Sept-Oct -2021)
 Zuitt Coding Bootcamp - 134 Timog Ave,
 Sacred Heart Quezon City

College

- Bachelor of Science: Electronics Engineering (2019-2021) Cebu Institute of Technology -University - Natalio Bacalso Avenue, Cebu City
- Bachelor of Science: Mechatronics (2015-2019) Cebu Technological University - M.J. Cuenco Avenue R. Palma St., Cebu City

High School & Elementary

• Three H Childhood Academy (2005- 2015)